---= GANDCRAB =---

Attention!
All your files documents, photos, databases and other important files are encrypted and have the extension: .GDCB 
The only method of recovering files is to purchase a private key. It is on our server and only we can recover your files.
The server with your key is in a closed network TOR. You can get there by the following ways:
1. Download Tor browser - https://www.torproject.org/
2. Install Tor browser
3. Open Tor Browser
4. Open link in tor browser: http://gdcbghvjyqy7jclk.onion/e4262665b23c5350                          
5. Follow the instructions on this page


If Tor/Tor browser is locked in your country or you can not install it, open one of the following links in your regular browser:
1. http://gdcbghvjyqy7jclk.onion.top/e4262665b23c5350                  
2. http://gdcbghvjyqy7jclk.onion.casa/e4262665b23c5350                 
3. http://gdcbghvjyqy7jclk.onion.guide/e4262665b23c5350                   
4. http://gdcbghvjyqy7jclk.onion.rip/e4262665b23c5350                                                 
5. http://gdcbghvjyqy7jclk.onion.plus/e4262665b23c5350                               

On our page you will see instructions on payment and get the opportunity to decrypt 1 file for free.

DANGEROUS!
Do not try to modify files or use your own private key - this will result in the loss of your data forever!
